Finding Aid for the Recordings of Creative Associates Recitals, 1964-1980
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel to reel tapes, 1964-1980, I.; Reel 1-Reel 172
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 87, April 16, 1975, 1 10-inch reel (Box 11) and 1 7-inch reel (Box 2); ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 11, 2, Reel 124-125)
    Work number: ubmu0063_124_05
    Boulez, Pierre
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute, Joseph Kubera, piano
    Duration: 17:54
    Cassette backup: CA 476
    Work number: ubmu0063_125_01
    Schwitters, Kurt
    Ursonate (1922-32)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, voice
    Duration: 25:28
    Cassette backup: CA 477
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 88, April 19, 1975, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips; Engineer's note: "wide separation" (Box 12, Reel 126)
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_01
    Hauer, Josef Matthias
    Nachlangstudien, op. 16 (1919)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, piano
    Duration: 5:07
    Cassette backup: CA 478
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_02
    Atonale Musik, op. 20 (1922)
    Duration: 14:49
    Cassette backup: CA 479
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_03
    Etude, op. 22, no. 3 (1922)
    Duration: 5:14
    Cassette backup: CA 480
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_04
    Praludium for Celesta (1921)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, celesta
    Cassette backup: CA 481
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_05
    Zwolftonspiele no. 1 (April 1947)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, harpsichord
    Duration: 1:09
    Cassette backup: CA 482
    Note: Engineer's note: Missed first two seconds.
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_06
    Zwolftonspiele no. 2 (April 1947)
    Duration: 2:12
    Cassette backup: CA 483
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_07
    Hauer, Joseph Matthias
    Zwolftonspiele no. 3 (August 1948)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, Harpsichord; Eberhard Blum, flute
    Cassette backup: CA 484
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_08
    Zwolftonspiele no. 4 (April 1947)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, harpsichord; Theresa Stahl, viola
    Duration: 2:44
    Cassette backup: CA 485
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_09
    Zwolftonspiele no. 5 (New Year's 1947)
    Cassette backup: CA 486
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_10
    Zwolftonspiele no. 6 (July 1952)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, Steven Radecke, piano
    Duration: 1:44
    Cassette backup: CA 487
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_11
    Zwolftonspiele no. 7 (New Year's 1947)
    Performers: Gary Hatt, clarinet
    Cassette backup: CA 488
    Work number: ubmu0063_126_12
    Zwolftonspiele no. 8: Labyrinthischer Tanz (November 1952)
    Cassette backup: CA 489
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 89, January 21, 1976, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips; Note: there was not supposed to be applause at this concert so works are separated only by silence (Box 12, Reel 127)
    Work number: ubmu0063_127_01
    Sonata, piano, no. 23, op. 57, F minor. Allegro assai
    Duration: 11:56
    Cassette backup: CA 490
    Work number: ubmu0063_127_02
    Wasser Klavier (1965)
    Duration: 3:45
    Cassette backup: CA 491
    Work number: ubmu0063_127_03
    Music for Marcel Duchamp (1947)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, prepared piano
    Cassette backup: CA 492
    Work number: ubmu0063_127_04
    Mare Serenitatis (1972)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, Steven Radecke, James Calabrese, Yvar Mikhashoff, pianos
    Duration: 10:09
    Cassette backup: CA 493
    Work number: ubmu0063_127_05
    Duration: 3:34
    Cassette backup: CA 494
    Work number: ubmu0063_127_06
    Pianos and voices
    Performers: Martha Hanneman, Elaine Marie Sheehan, Colleen Gibbons, Elaine Moise, Joan Collopy, voices; Joseph Kubera, Steven Radecke, Marcella Faine, James Calabrese, John Newell, pianos
    Duration: 22:04
    Cassette backup: CA 495
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 90, February 1, 1976, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 12, Reel 128-129)
    Work number: ubmu0063_128_01
    Toccata in G. Canzona in A minor
    Performers: Nora Post, baroque oboe; David Fuller, harpsichord
    Cassette backup: CA 496
    Note: Two works on one file.
    Work number: ubmu0063_128_02
    Sonata, oboe, continuo, E-flat major
    Cassette backup: CA 497
    Note: Four movements.
    Work number: ubmu0063_128_03
    Le Rossignol-en-amour. Double du Rossignol
    Duration: 4:19
    Cassette backup: CA 498
    Work number: ubmu0063_128_04
    Les Musetes de Choisi et de Taverni
    Duration: 5:47
    Cassette backup: CA 499
    Work number: ubmu0063_129_01
    Nemiroff, Isaac
    Atomyriades (1972)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe
    Cassette backup: CA 500
    Work number: ubmu0063_129_02
    Casavant, Charles
    Vocalise II (1975)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Joseph Kubera, piano; Walter Gajewski, electronics
    Duration: 19:19
    Cassette backup: CA 501
    Work number: ubmu0063_129_03
    Sequenza VII (1969)
    Cassette backup: CA 502
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 91, February 18, 1976, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 12, Reel 130)
    Work number: ubmu0063_130_01
    Sequenza I (1958)
    Duration: 7:10
    Cassette backup: CA 503
    Work number: ubmu0063_130_02
    Bertoncini, Mario
    Tune (1965)
    Duration: 11:37
    Cassette backup: CA 504
    Work number: ubmu0063_130_03
    Grosskopf, Erhard Georg
    Nexus (1968)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute, piccolo; Jan Williams, percussion; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 18:42
    Cassette backup: CA 505
    Work number: ubmu0063_130_04
    Shun-san (1969)
    Duration: 9:42
    Cassette backup: CA 506
    Work number: ubmu0063_130_05
    Chihara, Paul
    Willow, Willow (1968)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, bass flute; Don Harry, tuba; Jan Williams, Donald Knaack, John Boudler, percussion
    Duration: 12:13
    Cassette backup: CA 507
    Work number: ubmu0063_130_06
    Kagel, Mauricio
    Atem (1970)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Jan Williams, actor
    Duration: 13:09
    Cassette backup: CA 508
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 92, March 3, 1976, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 12, Reel 131)
    Work number: ubmu0063_131_01
    Bode, Harald
    Sequence III (1976)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, percussion
    Duration: 5:54
    Cassette backup: CA 509
    Work number: ubmu0063_131_02
    Cadenza (1972)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, piano interior
    Cassette backup: CA 510
    Work number: ubmu0063_131_03
    27'10.554" for a percussionist (1956)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, percussion; Linda Swiniuch, dancer; Walter Gajewski, electronics
    Duration: 30:41
    Cassette backup: CA 511
    Note: Includes spoken word comments.
    Work number: ubmu0063_131_04
    Fantasia Concertante (1975)
    Duration: 12:23
    Cassette backup: CA 512
    Work number: ubmu0063_131_05
    Knaack, Donald and Gajewski, Walter
    B.O.D.E. - 88.7 (1975-76)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, percussion; Walter Gajewski, live electronics
    Duration: 15:53
    Cassette backup: CA 513
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 93, September 29, 1976, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 12, Reel 132)
    Work number: ubmu0063_132_01
    Bach, Carl Philipp Emanuel
    Sonata, flute alone, W.132, A minor
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute
    Duration: 11:31
    Cassette backup: CA 514
    Note: Three movements.
    Work number: ubmu0063_132_02
    Gaubert, Philippe
    Scherzando and Allegro
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 6:34
    Cassette backup: CA 515
    Work number: ubmu0063_132_03
    Duration: 9:20
    Cassette backup: CA 516
    Work number: ubmu0063_132_04
    Petrassi, Goffredo
    Souffle for Flute Solo (1969)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute, alto flute, piccolo
    Cassette backup: CA 517
    Work number: ubmu0063_132_05
    Jolivet, Andre
    Suite en Concert, flute, percussion
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Timothy Leaphart, Donald Knaack, Gregory Ketchum, Robert Mahoney, percussion
    Duration: 17:52
    Cassette backup: CA 518
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 94, November 10, 1976, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 12, Reel 133)
    Work number: ubmu0063_133_01
    Riley, Howard
    Shaped (1976)
    Performers: Howard Riley, piano
    Duration: 43:42
    Cassette backup: CA 519
    Note: Solo piano improvisation.
    Work number: ubmu0063_133_02
    Gajewski, Walter; Ketchum, Gregory; Riley, Howard
    Sounding (1976)
    Performers: Howard Riley, piano; Walter Gajewski, electronics; Gregory Ketchum, percussion
    Duration: 31:48
    Cassette backup: CA 520
    Note: Group improvisation.
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 95, January 26, 1977, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 12, Reel 134)
    Work number: ubmu0063_134_01
    Gajewski, Walter
    Na ja, Hier Waren Wir Also (1976)
    Performers: Colleen Gibbons, voice; Gary Storm, viola; Walter Gajewski, accordion
    Duration: 4:27
    Cassette backup: CA 522
    Note: Not transferred to cassette.
    Work number: ubmu0063_134_02
    Politics (1977)
    Performers: Raymond Federman, Colleen Gibbons, Gary Storm, voices; Tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 10:26
    Cassette backup: CA 523
    Work number: ubmu0063_134_03
    Flute from the Hip (1977)
    Performers: Henryk Svitzer, flute; Tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 14:15
    Cassette backup: CA 524
    Work number: ubmu0063_134_04
    Viola Vipers (1977)
    Performers: Gary Storm, electric viola
    Cassette backup: CA 525
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 96, February 24, 1977, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 12, Reel 135)
    Work number: ubmu0063_135_01
    Requiem for John Cage on the Chants "John Cage is Dead"
    Cassette backup: CA 527
    Work number: ubmu0063_135_02
    Na ja, hier waren wir also (1976)
    Duration: 3:00
    Cassette backup: CA 528
    Work number: ubmu0063_135_03
    Cassette backup: CA 529
    Work number: ubmu0063_135_04
    Stereo Demonstration a la 1957 (1977)
    Performers: Walter Gajewski, assistant; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 9:35
    Cassette backup: CA 530
    Work number: ubmu0063_135_05
    Duration: 15:52
    Cassette backup: CA 531
    Work number: ubmu0063_135_06
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 23:35
    Cassette backup: CA 532
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 99, April 20, 1977, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 12-13, Reel 136-137)
    Work number: ubmu0063_136_01
    Sonata, piano, no. 29, op. 106, B-flat major
    Performers: Frederic Rzewski, piano
    Duration: 52:04
    Cassette backup: CA 545
    Note: Preceded by spoken comments by Fredric Rzewski.
    Work number: ubmu0063_137_01
    Rzewski, Frederic
    People United Will Never Be Defeated
    Duration: 1:03:14
    Cassette backup: CA 546
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 100, May 18, 1977, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 13, Reel 138)
    Work number: ubmu0063_138_01
    Ciaccona, Intermezzo, e Adagio (1945)
    Performers: Frances-Marie Uitti, violoncello
    Duration: 17:31
    Cassette backup: CA 547
    Work number: ubmu0063_138_02
    Solo de "La Passion Selon Sade" (1966)
    Duration: 4:46
    Cassette backup: CA 548
    Work number: ubmu0063_138_03
    Sensitivio per Arco Solo (1968)
    Cassette backup: CA 549
    Work number: ubmu0063_138_04
    Sciarrino, Salvatore
    Due Studi per Violoncello Solo (1974)
    Cassette backup: CA 550
    Work number: ubmu0063_138_05
    Scelsi, Giacinto
    Triphon (1956) (tre pezzi)
    Duration: 15:15
    Cassette backup: CA 551
    Work number: ubmu0063_138_06
    Dithome (1957)
    Duration: 13:00
    Cassette backup: CA 552
    Work number: ubmu0063_138_07
    Ygghur (1964)
    Duration: 16:34
    Cassette backup: CA 553
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 101, May 21, 1977, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 13, Reel 139-140)
    Work number: ubmu0063_139_01
    Syrinx
    Duration: 4:15
    Cassette backup: CA 554
    Note: Preceded by spoken comments by Henrik Svitzer.
    Work number: ubmu0063_139_02
    Norholm, Ib
    3 pieces For Flute and Organ, op. 37a (1966)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Michael Burke, organ
    Duration: 13:34
    Cassette backup: CA 555
    Note: Preceded by spoken comments by Michael Burke.
    Work number: ubmu0063_139_03
    Berg, Gunnar
    Filandre (1953)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Gary Hatt, clarinet
    Duration: 14:53
    Cassette backup: CA 556
    Work number: ubmu0063_139_04
    Sonata, flute, viola, harp
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Diane Williams, viola; Suzanne Thomas, harp
    Duration: 19:31
    Cassette backup: CA 557
    Work number: ubmu0063_140_01
    Duration: 5:42
    Cassette backup: CA 558
    Work number: ubmu0063_140_02
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Charles Clifton, piano
    Duration: 5:23
    Cassette backup: CA 559
    Note: Preceded by spoken comments by Henrik Svitzer
    Work number: ubmu0063_140_03
    Les Nodes Argentees (1975)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Suzanne Thomas, harp
    Duration: 12:57
    Cassette backup: CA 560
    Work number: ubmu0063_140_04
    Tropi (1959)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Gary Hatt, clarinet; violin; Mary Sue Wells, violoncello; Charles Clifton, piano; Jan Williams, percussion
    Cassette backup: CA 561
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 102, September 21, 1977, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 13, Reel 141-142)
    Work number: ubmu0063_141_01
    Sonata, oboe, continuo, W. 135, G minor
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Leo Smit, harpsichord
    Cassette backup: CA 562
    Work number: ubmu0063_141_02
    Cantata no. 187: Es wartet alles auf dich. Gott versorget alles Lebeng
    Performers: Martha Hanneman, soprano; Nora Post, oboe; Leo Smit, harpsichord
    Cassette backup: CA 563A
    Work number: ubmu0063_141_03
    Cantata No. 199: Mein Herze schwimmt im Blut. Wie freudig ist mein Herz
    Duration: 2:39
    Cassette backup: CA 563B
    Work number: ubmu0063_141_04
    Marcello, Alessandro
    Concerto, oboe, string orchestra, D minor
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Marie Yadzinski, Sue Harbison, violins; Diane Williams, viola; Mary Sue Wells, violoncello
    Duration: 13:14
    Cassette backup: CA 564
    Work number: ubmu0063_142_01
    Fischer, Johann
    Rondeau
    Duration: 4:38
    Cassette backup: CA 565
    Work number: ubmu0063_142_02
    Quartet, oboe, string, K. 368b (370), F major
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Marie Yadzinski; violin; Diane Williams, viola; Mary Sue Wells, violoncello
    Duration: 18:15
    Cassette backup: CA 566
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 103, November 12, 1977, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 13, Reel 143)
    Work number: ubmu0063_143_01
    Kurtz, Eugene
    Last Contra Bass in Las Vegas
    Performers: Carol Plantamura, soprano; Joelle Leandre, double bass
    Duration: 11:25
    Cassette backup: CA 567
    Work number: ubmu0063_143_02
    Logs (1969)
    Performers: Joelle Leandre, double bass; Ralph Jones, electronics
    Duration: 8:28
    Cassette backup: CA 568
    Work number: ubmu0063_143_03
    Leandre, Joelle
    F.A. (1977)
    Performers: Joelle Leandre, double bass
    Duration: 9:31
    Cassette backup: CA 569
    Work number: ubmu0063_143_04
    Valentine (1969)
    Duration: 12:04
    Cassette backup: CA 570
    Work number: ubmu0063_143_05
    Concert for flute, contrabass, and piano with Fontana Mix and Solo For Voice 1 (1958)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Joelle Leandre, double bass and voice; John Tilbury, piano; Ralph Jones, electronics
    Duration: 16:53
    Cassette backup: CA 571
    Work number: ubmu0063_143_06
    Temoignage (1976)
    Cassette backup: CA 572
    Work number: ubmu0063_143_07
    Mott, David Howard
    Night Flowers II, IV, V (1973)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Joelle Leandre, double bass
    Cassette backup: CA 573
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 104, November 17, 1977, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 13, Reel 144-145)
    Work number: ubmu0063_144_01
    Matthews, William
    Diora sarabanda (1974)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute
    Duration: 5:26
    Cassette backup: CA 574
    Work number: ubmu0063_144_02
    Morris, Robert Daniel
    Raudra (1977)
    Duration: 3:06
    Cassette backup: CA 575
    Work number: ubmu0063_144_03
    Duration: 11:23
    Cassette backup: CA 576
    Work number: ubmu0063_144_04
    Rucke di guck (1955)
    Performers: Robert Dick, piccolo; Nora Post, oboe
    Duration: 10:21
    Cassette backup: CA 577
    Work number: ubmu0063_145_01
    Dick, Robert
    Smoker (1977)
    Performers: Robert Dick, amplified bass flute
    Cassette backup: CA 578
    Work number: ubmu0063_145_02
    Force (1976)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Joelle Leandre, double bass; Gregory Ketchum, percussion
    Cassette backup: CA 579
    Work number: ubmu0063_145_03
    Time Line (1977)
    Duration: 15:02
    Cassette backup: CA 580
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 105, December 2, 1977, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 13, Reel 146-147)
    Work number: ubmu0063_146_01
    Sonatas and Interludes, piano
    Performers: John Tilbury, prepared piano
    Duration: 38:13
    Cassette backup: CA 581
    Work number: ubmu0063_147_01
    Riley, Terry
    Dorian Reeds
    Performers: John Tilbury, electric organ
    Duration: 28:49
    Cassette backup: CA 582
    Work number: ubmu0063_147_02
    Musikalisches Opfer. Ricercar a 6
    Performers: John Tilbury, piano
    Duration: 8:53
    Cassette backup: CA 583
    Work number: ubmu0063_147_03
    Sechs kleine Klavierstucke, op. 19
    Duration: 4:51
    Cassette backup: CA 584
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 106, January 27, 1978, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 13-14, Reel 148-149)
    Work number: ubmu0063_148_01
    Asia, Daniel Isaac
    Plum-Dream Sequence (1977)
    Duration: 8:24
    Cassette backup: CA 585
    Work number: ubmu0063_148_02
    Walk (1976)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Stephen Manes, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 586
    Work number: ubmu0063_148_03
    McTee, Cindy
    Chord (1977)
    Duration: 7:46
    Cassette backup: CA 587
    Work number: ubmu0063_148_04
    Messiaen, Olivier
    Le Merle Noir (1952)
    Duration: 6:27
    Cassette backup: CA 588
    Work number: ubmu0063_149_01
    Duration: 8:49
    Cassette backup: CA 589
    Work number: ubmu0063_149_02
    Paganini, Nicolo
    Caprice, violin alone, op. 1, no. 15, E minor, arranged
    Duration: 3:54
    Cassette backup: CA 590A
    Work number: ubmu0063_149_03
    Caprice, violin alone, op. 1, no. 2, B minor, arranged
    Cassette backup: CA 590B
    Work number: ubmu0063_149_04
    MacCombie, Bruce Franklin
    Found Objects (1977)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute and bass flute; Bruce MacCombie, prepared piano
    Duration: 9:00
    Cassette backup: CA 591
    Work number: ubmu0063_149_05
    Biscardi, Chester
    Tenzone (1976)
    Performers: Robert Dick, Mary Luehresen, flutes; Stephen Manes, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 592
    Work number: ubmu0063_149_06
    Cassette backup: CA 593
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 107, March 1, 1978, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 14, Reel 150)
    Work number: ubmu0063_150_01
    Piechowska, Alina
    Amitus Sonore (1972)
    Performers: Weronika Knittel, violin
    Cassette backup: CA 594
    Work number: ubmu0063_150_02
    Miniatures (1959)
    Performers: Weronika Knittel, violin, Krzysztof Knittel, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 595
    Work number: ubmu0063_150_03
    Bacewicz, Grazyna
    Sonata (1958)
    Duration: 10:43
    Cassette backup: CA 596
    Work number: ubmu0063_150_04
    Knittel, Krzysztof
    Conqueror Worm (1976)
    Performers: Tape made in the Experimental Studio of Polish Radio in Warsaw.
    Duration: 13:49
    Cassette backup: CA 597
    Work number: ubmu0063_150_05
    Sikora, Elzbieta; Knittel, Krzysztof and Michniewski, Wojciech
    Third Secret Poem (1974)
    Duration: 16:36
    Cassette backup: CA 598
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 108, March 23, 1978, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 14, Reel 151)
    Work number: ubmu0063_151_01
    Carr, Adrian
    Three Pieces for Flute and percussion
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Erik Jacobson, percussion
    Duration: 14:27
    Cassette backup: CA 599
    Work number: ubmu0063_151_02
    Trede, Yngve
    Dialogues for Flute and percussion (1978)
    Cassette backup: CA 600
    Work number: ubmu0063_151_03
    So to Say (1978)
    Duration: 15:31
    Cassette backup: CA 601
    Work number: ubmu0063_151_04
    Norgard, Per
    Waves
    Performers: Erik Jacobson, percussion
    Duration: 15:20
    Cassette backup: CA 602
    Work number: ubmu0063_151_05
    Mating Dance (1977)
    Duration: 15:18
    Cassette backup: CA 603
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 109, April 13, 1978, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 14, Reel 152)
    Work number: ubmu0063_152_01
    Standing (1973)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Weronika Knittel, violin; Gregory Ketchum, percussion
    Duration: 7:28
    Cassette backup: CA 604
    Work number: ubmu0063_152_02
    Performers: Gary Hatt, clarinet; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 14:06
    Cassette backup: CA 605
    Work number: ubmu0063_152_03
    Duration: 6:24
    Cassette backup: CA 606
    Work number: ubmu0063_152_04
    Orient Orientation (1973)
    Performers: Robert Dick, Cheryl Gobbetti, flutes
    Cassette backup: CA 607
    Work number: ubmu0063_152_05
    Luster Gave Her Hat and He and Ben Went Across the Backyard
    Performers: Gregory Ketchum, Albert Furness, Michael Pugliese, marimbas
    Duration: 15:09
    Cassette backup: CA 608
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 110, April 19, 1978, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 14, Reel 153)
    Work number: ubmu0063_153_01
    Rands, Bernard
    Memo I (1971)
    Duration: 9:57
    Cassette backup: CA 609
    Work number: ubmu0063_153_02
    Duration: 9:08
    Cassette backup: CA 610
    Work number: ubmu0063_153_03
    Gremaud, Stephane
    Miroir (1977)
    Performers: Stephane Gremaud, percussion
    Cassette backup: CA 611
    Work number: ubmu0063_153_04
    Wonderful Widow of Eighteen Springs (1942)
    Performers: Joelle Leandre, double bass; tape realized by the composer
    Cassette backup: CA 612
    Work number: ubmu0063_153_05
    Richer, Jeannine
    Ligne interrompue
    Duration: 15:23
    Cassette backup: CA 613
    Work number: ubmu0063_153_06
    Verdi, Giuseppe
    Othello (sans date ou creation mondiale)
    Duration: 3:10
    Cassette backup: CA 614
    Work number: ubmu0063_153_07
    Duration: 10:24
    Cassette backup: CA 615
    Work number: ubmu0063_153_08
    Leandre, Joelle and Gremaud, Stephane
    Porte-Ferme (1978)
    Performers: Joelle Leandre, double bass; Stephane Gremaud, percussion
    Duration: 8:18
    Cassette backup: CA 616
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 111, May 10, 1978, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 14, Reel 154-155)
    Work number: ubmu0063_154_01-04
    Vesty, Dwight, and Ketchum, Gregory
    Prelude to "SST", Bann the "SST"
    Performers: James Hayes, Walter Hunt, Albert Furness, Michael Pugliese, percussion
    Duration: 57:34
    Cassette backup: CA 617-620
    Work number: ubmu0063_155_01
    Lirio (1971)
    Performers: (Performers not Listed)
    Duration: 36:46
    Cassette backup: CA 621
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 112, May 11, 1978, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 14, Reel 156)
    Work number: ubmu0063_156_01
    Form A, E (1973)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Duane Saetveit, horn; Darlene Reynard, bassoon
    Duration: 13:04
    Cassette backup: CA 622
    Work number: ubmu0063_156_02
    A la Sante, 1974